USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  - Subseries 2: USS Arizona and Personnel Photographs, 1916-1941
    - Gloria Stuart on Deck of USS Arizona During Filming of Here Comes the Navy, 77-3-316, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Gloria Stuart and Unidentified Actors on Deck of USS Arizona During Filming of Here Comes the Navy, 77-3-317, 1934 April (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Lloyd Bacon, Pat O'Brien, Gloria Stuart, Captain Milne, USN, James Cagney, Frank McHugh on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-318, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Saturday Evening Post Illustration, 77-3-319, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Saturday Evening Post Illustration, 77-3-320, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - USS Arizona Band in Boston, MA, 77-3-321, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - USS Arizona Band and Bugle Corps Group Photograph, 77-3-322, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - United States Navy Blimp in Flight, 77-3-323, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Airplanes on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-3-324, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Pilot Standing on top of Plane, 77-3-325, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Pilot Standing on top of Plane in Water, 77-3-326, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Pilot Standing on top of Plane above USS Arizona Deck, 77-3-327, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Tradewind Airplane on Beach, 77-3-328, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Airplane Launched from Catapult, 77-3-329, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Pilot Standing on top of Plane in Water, 77-3-330, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Aerial Smoke Screen, 77-3-331, circa 1934 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Eyes of the Fleet, 77-3-332, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Amphibian Plane Leaving Battleship Catapult, 77-3-333, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Launching Plane from Deck Catapult, 77-3-334, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Navy Dirigible Moored to USS Patoka, 77-3-335, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Eyes of the Fleet in Line Formation, 77-3-336, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - An IF Flying Squadron, 77-3-337, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - PN9 Flying over San Diego Bay, 77-3-338, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Refueling in the Air, 77-3-339, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Taking Off From Flying Deck of Airplane Carrier, 77-3-340, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Airplane View of the Los Angeles Dirigible, 77-3-341, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Dropping Aerial Torpedo, 77-3-342, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Navy Ambulance Plane, 77-3-343, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bombing Plane Formation, 77-3-344, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Double Parachute Jump, 77-3-345, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Parachute Jump from Navy Plane, 77-3-346, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Inspection T4M Bombing and Torpedo Planes, 77-3-347, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Large Building Fire Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-348, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Night View of Large Building Fire Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-349, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Aerial View of Fire Damage to Building Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-350, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Street View of Fire Damage to Building Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-351, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Street View of Fire Damage to Building Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-352, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Street View of Fire Damage to Building Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-353, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Damage to Seaside Hospital Caused by Long Beach, CA Earthquake, 77-3-354, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Ruins at Long Beach Caused by Earthquake, 77-3-355, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Ocean Avenue, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-356, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Poly-High, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-357, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Ruins at Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-358, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Hamilton School, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-359, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Ruins of Security Building, Compton, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-360, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Ruins at Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-361, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - The Pike, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-362, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Hotel Ruins, Compton, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-363, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Feeding Refugees at Lincoln Park, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-364, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Ruins of Catholic Church, Long Beach, CA, 77-3-365, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Fifth and Front Streets, San Pedro, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-366, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Imperial Theater, Ocean Avenue, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-367, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Anaheim Boulevard, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-368, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Law Enforcement by U.S. Navy, Long Beach, CA after Earthquake, 77-3-369, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Vehicle Damage Caused by Earthquake, 77-3-370, 1933 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Colonel William Prescott Monument, Charleston, MA, 77-3-371, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Colonel William Prescott Monument Statue, Charleston, MA, 77-3-372, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - USS Constitution at Dock, 77-3-373, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - USS Constitution at Dock, 77-3-374, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - USS Constitution at Dock, 77-3-375, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - USS Constitution at Dock, 77-3-376, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Washington Monument, Washington, D.C., 77-3-377, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - U.S Capitol, Washington, D.C., 77-3-378, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - National Museum, Washington, D.C., 77-3-379, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Lincoln Memorial, Washington, D.C., 77-3-380, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Whitehouse from Washington Monument, Washington, D.C., 77-3-381, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Main Entrance to Whitehouse, Washington, D.C., 77-3-382, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Washington's Home, Mt. Vernon, 77-3-386, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - U.S. Treasury Building, Washington, D.C., 77-3-384, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Whitehouse, Washington, D.C., 77-3-385, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - View of Capitol from Washington Monument, Washington, D.C., 77-3-386, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Washington's Home, Mt. Vernon, VA, 77-3-387, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Lincoln Memorial, 77-3-388, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - 1790 Convict Ship, The Oldest Ship in the World, 77-3-389, circa 1933 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Deck of 1790 Convict Ship, 77-3-390, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bow of USS Arizona, 77-3-391, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, 77-3-392, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona in Dry Dock, 77-3-393, circa 1933 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Railway Yard, Panama, 77-3-394, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Old French Canal, Panama Canal, 77-3-395, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Coconut Grove, Panama City, Republic of Panama, 77-3-396, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Church, 77-3-397, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Cathedral in Panama, 77-3-398, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Old Prison, Panama City, Republic of Panama, 77-3-399, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Central Avenue, Panama City, Republic of Panama, 77-3-400, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Ruins of San Domingo Church, Panama City, Republic of Panama, 77-3-401, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Panamanian Children, 77-3-402, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Golden Altar in San Jose Church, Panama City, Republic of Panama, 77-3-403, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Ruins of Old Panama, 77-3-404, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Rice Farmer's Home, Oahu, HI, 77-3-405, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Cocoa Palms, Oahu, T.H., 77-3-406, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Cocoa Palms, Waianae Golf Course, Honolulu, HI, 77-3-407, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Sampans, Honolulu, HI, 77-3-408, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Native Outrigger Canoe, Hawaii, 77-3-409, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Rainbow Falls, Hilo, HI, 77-3-410, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Fleet at Anchor in Lahaina Roads, Maui, February 14, 1932, Navy Propaganda Photograph (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Fleet at Anchor at San Pedro, Navy Propaganda Photograph,77-3-412, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Destroyers Maneuvering, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-413, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Battle Force Practice, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-414, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Scrubbing Deck of USS Texas Battleship, 77-3-415, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Recreation Room on U.S. Battleship, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-416, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Destroyers Laying Smoke Screen, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-417, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - A Cozy Bed for Tabby, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-418, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Sailors Playing Backgammon on Deck of Unidentified Ship, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-419, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Liberty Party, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-420, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Mail for Everybody, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-421, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Navy Diver Coming Up, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-422, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Turret Crew Getting Prize Money, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-423, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Honest John an Unusual Mascot, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-424, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - A Friendly Game, Sailors Playing Card Game, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-425, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Mess Cook Parade, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-426, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Skylarking, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-427, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - The Crews Pets, Sailor with Puppy and Sea Turtle, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-428, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - A Gentle Pet, Unidentified Sailor Holding Bobcat, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-429, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Wrecked Destroyers on Point Honda, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-430, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Gunnery Practice, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-431, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Baseball Practice at Sea, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-432, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - The Long and Short of It, Two Unidentified Sailors Holding Tubas, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-433, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Battleships in Column Formation, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-434, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Water Taxis at Captains Conference, Navy Propaganda Photograph, 77-3-435, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - USS Arizona in Norfolk Navy Yard Dry Dock During Modernization, 77-3-436, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - The Old Kearsarge, 77-3-437, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Fleet Searchlight Display, San Pedro, CA, September, 1931, 77-3-438 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Plane Taking off, USS Lexington, 77-3-439, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Mt. Rainer, Seattle, WA, 77-3-440, circa 1932 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Remember 'Em on the Arizona?, Newspaper Photograph of 1923-1927 USS Arizona Boxing Team, 77-7-3, circa 1932 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Battleships In Formation, 77-7-4, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - View of Unidentified Battleship at Sea taken from USS Arizona, 77-7-5, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bow of USS Pensacola, 77-7-6, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - View of Ocean, 77-7-7, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - View of Ocean, 77-7-8, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - View of Flagstaff on USS Pensacola Bow, 77-7-9, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Wave Hitting USS Pensacola Bow, 77-7-10, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bow of USS Pensacola, 77-7-11, circa 1922 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Panama Tough, Man on Panama Street, 77-7-12, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Electric Mule's, Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-13, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Native Houses on Stilts Along the Panama Canal, 77-7-14, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Safety Gate, Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-15, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-16, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - USS Arizona Forecastle, 77-7-17, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-18, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-19, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - View of Panama Canal from Dock of Ship, 77-7-20, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Panama Canal, 77-7-21, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-22, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Sailors on Dock of Ship Passing through Panama Canal, 77-7-23, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Panama Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-24, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - View along the Panama Canal, 77-7-25, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - View from Ship Passing through Panama Canal, 77-7-26, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Crew on deck of USS Arizona as it Passes through Panama Canal, 7-7-27, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified Ship Headed Eastward through Panama Canal, 7-7-28, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Gatun Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-29, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Gatun Locks, Panama Canal, 77-7-30, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Halemaumau, HI, 77-7-31, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Visitors aboard USS Arizona, Seattle, WA, 77-7-32, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - View of Seattle, WA from USS Arizona, 77-7-33, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - USS Arizona Light Display during Fleet Week, Seattle, WA, 77-7-34, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 77-7-35, circa 1925 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona #1 and #2 Turrets, 77-7-36, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Ship on Fire, 77-7-37, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Sailors in USS Arizona Engine Room, 77-7-38, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Sailors in USS Arizona Engine Room, 77-7-39, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-40, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Sailors Meyer and Black on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-41, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Sailor Black on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-42, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Sailor Albert Myers on Deck of USS Arizona as it Passes Through Panama Canal, 77-7-43, 1924 January 25 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors Standing in Field, 77-7-44, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Sailor Brooks on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-45, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Sailor Boyle on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-46, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Sailors on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-47, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Sailors LaVerne, Meyers, Lindsey, Brown, Shi, Baker, Clemen on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-48, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Members on USS Arizona Turrets, 77-7-49, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Al Meyers and two Unidentified Apprentices on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-50, circa 1929 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on Ship, 77-7-51, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Seven Sailors in front of a House, 77-7-52, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Sailors Ross and Padis in Panama City, Panama Restaurant, 77-7-53, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sailors Meyer and Kelso Playing on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-54, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sailors Meyer and Kelso Playing on Deck of USS Arizona, 77-7-55, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Sailors Meyer, Kelso, and Polack Sitting on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-56, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-57, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Sailor Eating a Turkey Leg on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-58, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Five Sailors Relaxing on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-59, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing in front of Hibiscus Plant, 77-7-60, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Sailor on Boat, 77-7-61, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - 3rd Class Machinists on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-62, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Sailor Al Meyers on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-63, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Sailors Murphy, Black, and Melvin on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-64, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Sailors Ross and Rodio Drinking in Restaurant, 77-7-65, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Sailors Ross and Rodio, 77-7-66, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Sailor Ross, 77-7-67, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Sailors Benedetto and Brooks on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-68, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Sailors Benedetto and Brooks on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-69, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Sailor Ross on Beach, 77-7-70, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Thirteen Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-71, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Sailors Putman and Joe Potenza on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-72, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Sailor Stocks on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-73, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Red Strip Engineering Crew - Sailors Beaudreaux, Russel, Unysho, and Inzen on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-74, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Unidentified Sailor Standing in Front of Searchlight at Night, 77-7-75, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Sailor Stocks, 77-7-76, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-77, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - 1st Class Petty Office Joe P. on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-78, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Two Unidentified Sailors on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-79, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Sailor Fritz on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-80, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Sailor Fritz on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-81, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - An Unidentified USS Arizona Electrician Standing in front of a House, 77-7-82, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Nine Sailors in the USS Arizona Engine Room, 77-7-83, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Sailors Tharp and Hooper on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-84, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Sailor Ross in Three Piece Suit, 77-7-85, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Sailors Jip, Al Meyer, and Slatts on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-86, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Sailors Joe Lindsay and Pomeroy on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-87, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Sailor Putnam on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-88, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Sailor Jip in swimsuit on Beach, 77-7-89, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Sailor Witick Standing on Beach, 77-7-90, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Sailors Joe Lindsay and Leighty on USS Arizona deck, 77-7-91, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Three Sailors Swimming in Ocean, 77-7-92, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - USS Arizona 1920 Race Boat Crew, 77-7-93, circa 1920 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Sailors Stanley Shrobacewski and Brooks, and Unidentified Sailor on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-94, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified Marine Standing in front of a House in San Diego, CA, 77-7-95, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Sailors Shrobacewski and Brooks on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-96, circa 1927 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Sailor Al Meyer on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-97, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Sailors Red Lewis and Al Meyer on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-98, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Sailor Al Meyer on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-99, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Sailors Red Lewis, Jip, Slatts, and Al Meyer on USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-100, circa 1929 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Sailors Bribie and Jip Sharing a Beer, Camp Gaillard, Panama Canal, 77-7-101, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - View of Battleships in Seattle, WA Bay Taken from USS Arizona Deck, 77-7-102, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Two Battleships at Sea, 77-7-103, circa 1925 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Sailors Lue and Harrington, Long Beach, CA, Postcard, 84-20-1, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Portrait of Unidentified Fireman, Postcard, 84-20-2, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Sailors Joe and Margolis, Postcard, 84-20-3, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Chinese Restaurant Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-4, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona in Miraflores Locks, Panama Canal, Postcard, 84-20-5, circa 1925 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Leaving Pedro Miguel Locks, Panama Canal, January 20, 1921, Postcard, 84-20-6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Postcard, 84-20-7, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Postcard, 84-20-8, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona at Target Practice, Postcard, 84-20-9, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona 14 Inch Gun, Postcard, 84-20-10, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Sea Swells Over USS Arizona Bow, Postcard, 84-20-11, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Sailors on USS Arizona Bow, Postcard, 84-20-12, circa 1927 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, Postcard, 84-20-13, circa 1931 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - USS Arizona Diving Party at Sea, Postcard, 84-20-14, circa 1931 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-15, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - USS Hardship Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-16, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Square Your Hat! Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-17, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Joe Blow Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-18, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Brig Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-19, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - The Prayer of a Sailor, Postcard, 84-20-20, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Get off the Wet Deck! Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-21, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Got Change for a Five Chief? Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-22, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - I Wonder if the Ole Buzzard and his Inspection Party has Passed by Yet Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-23, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - I'm Just a Poor Mess Cook Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-24, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Psst Lend Me Your Shoes Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-25, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Just Putting the Kick in the Morning Jamoke Chief Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-26, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - I was Sitting Down Minding My Own Business Captain, and the Patrol Picked on Me Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-27, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - I am a After Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-28, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Tail Lights Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-29, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Going Down Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-30, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Look Mammy Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-31, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Oh Boy! What a Lei Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-32, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - USS Arizona Merry Christmas Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-33, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - USS Arizona Merry Christmas Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-34, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Bottoms Up Cartoon, Postcard, 84-20-35, circa 1935 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 84-26-11, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Plane Leaving Catapult on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-12, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Plane Leaving Catapult on USS Arizona Deck, 84-26-13, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Gun Crew Loading Five Inch Gun, 84-26-14, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Machine Gun Crew Loading Gun, 84-26-15, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Crew Firing Anti-Aircraft Guns at a Target in the Air, 84-26-16, circa 1929 (Box 23, Folder 6)